Y'all see what's going on, and right now is a very critical time.
We need to understand the reality of voting, not just the action behind it.
We are not voting for a person.
We're voting for a path forward.
We vote because there are real issues that are facing you, your community, your kids, etc.
You want to vote the best person for the path forward to dealing with those issues.
And I have partnered with the Black Futures Lab to spread the word about the Black Census.
Largest survey of Black people in America since the Reconstruction.
They want to know what are the voting issues that you care about.
And what is your experience like in this country as a Black person?
Because our issues matter even outside of an election year.
Please visit the link in my bio so that you can complete the census.
You have until October 15th.
Okay.
Please vote.
For a number of reasons.
You know, vote just to be petty.
Because the 14th Amendment said you a citizen and you should be able to vote.
And they have spent all of this effort trying to make sure that you don't vote,
even though they said you were supposed to be able to.
Vote because, baby, if your vote didn't matter,
they would not put all of this work in to suppress it.
The reality is we are not going to solve America in this next election.
But I believe we can vote for the best path forward to give us the time to attempt to do so.
We know that our voices need to be heard and the Black Census wants to hear from you.
So go to my link in bio before October 15th and fill it out.